Finding Aid for the Fletcher Bascom Dresslar Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Outgoing Correspondence Index
  - Thomas, Adelbert A., Aug. 26, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Aug. 28, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Aug. 28, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Blanton, R.S., Sept. 3, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Reid, Frank K., Sept. 3, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, Sept. 16, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rowe, L.S., Sept. 16, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Sept. 30, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Haaga, Theressa, Oct. 7, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Holt, Elizabeth C., Oct. 21, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Menon, K.B., Oct. 21, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Oct. 30, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Bruce, William C., Nov. 9, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 14, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, Nov. 14, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Jackson, Mrs. H.E., Nov. 23, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Bryan, William lowe, Nov. 29, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Nov. 29, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Dec. 30, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Moser, Mr., Jan. 3, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Braden, W.H., Jan. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Earley, Albert, Jan. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Menon, K.B., Jan. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Barber and McMurry, Architects, Jan. 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Chumber, Roy 0., Jan. 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Donovan, John J., Jan. 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Jenkins, F.C., Jan. 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Sibley, James E., Jan. 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Tucker, President, Jan. 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Ranck, F.E., Jan. 14, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Jenkins, Frank C., Jan. 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Brown, Allye Mae, Jan. 21, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach. L.A., Jan. 21, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Tucker, E.B., Jan. 21, 1927 (Box 3)
  - McAfee, L.F., Jan. 22, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Mennen, K.D., Jan. 22, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Sibley, James E., Jan. 22, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Smith, J.F., Jan. 22, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Stone, May, Jan. 22, 1927 (Box 3)
  - McCuistion, Fred, Jan. 26, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Ireland, Allen G., Jan. 27, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Mitchell, Morris, Jan. 27, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Braden, W.H., Jan. 28, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Jrouse, P.G., Jan. 28, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Jrouse, P.G., Jan. 29, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Jan. 29, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Buchner, Edward, Feb. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Shofstall, W.P., Feb. 19, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Butler, George D., Feb. 23, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Esper, George J., Feb. 23, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Feb. 28, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Chumber, Roy 0., March 1, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Smith, J.F., March 1, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Tucker, E.B., March 14, 192 (Box 3)
  - Palmore, R.A., March 21, 192 (Box 3)
  - Barber, Charles I., March 30, 192 (Box 3)
  - Hunkins, L.E., March 30, 192 (Box 3)
  - Swetman, Ralph W., March 30, 192 (Box 3)
  - Tucker, E.B., March 30, 192 (Box 3)
  - Burns, L.W., April 1, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Cralle, Robert E., April 1, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Hall, Mary, April 1, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Mulvihill, Philip, April 1, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., April 1, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Stone, May, April 1, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Lowery, Lawrence T., April 6, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Mozee, 8. 8., April 11, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Sandmeier, M.A., April 11, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Challman, Samuel A., April 15, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Cralle, Robert E., April 15, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Mulvihill, Philip, April 15, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Fenn, Donald F., April 20, 1927 (Box 3)
  - McCuistion, Fred, April 20, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Swetman, Ralph W., April 25, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Sydenham, Laura M., April 25, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Esper, George J., April 29, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., April 30, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Harmon, A.F., May 2, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Lowery, Lawrence T., May 3, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Berry, Mrs., May 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Tucker, E.B., May 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Adams, Robert H., May 20, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Henry, J.H., May 20, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Lowery, Lawrence T., May 20, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Hirst, C.M., May 25, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Lowrey, Lawrence T., May 25, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Henderson, Carrie, June 3, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Sweets, Henry H., June 3, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Woodward, R., June 3, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Brahan, T.S., June 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Tidwell, R.E., June 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Cook, Elmer, June 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Mowery, H.W., June 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Sanders, J.E., June 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Schiesz, L.B., June 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Wiggins, H.B., June 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Ganey, J.S., June 28, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., June 28, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Wiggins, H.B., June 28, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Wiggins, H.B., June 28, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Wiggins, H.B., July 1, 1927 (Box 3)
  - D.C. Heath and Co., July 2, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Tucker, E.B., July 8, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Blalock, Flora, July 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Foresman, Mary E., July 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Laird, P.E., July 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Smith, J.F., July 20, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Emerson, D.W., July 28, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Hardin, Jesse, July 28, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Lowrey, Dr., July 29, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., July 29, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Graham, James M., Aug. 2, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Hardin, Jesse, Aug. 2, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Hardin, Jesse, Aug. 2, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Williams, Zelia, Aug. 2, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Emerson, D.W., Aug. 12, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Challman, Samuel A., Aug. 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Manning, Mr., Aug. 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Hellenic Information Bureau, Aug. 24, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Smith, Professor, Aug. 27, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Aug. 30, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Brainerd, Heloise, Sept. 23, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Cullens, Helen, Sept. 23, 1927 (Box 3)
  - O'Shea, M.V., Sept. 23, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Shackelford, E.M., Sept. 23, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Smith, J.F., Sept. 23, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Blakely, H.B., Oct. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Dittmar, Mr., Oct. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Hull, Emmett J., Oct. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Menon, H.B., Oct. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Menon, H.B., Oct. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Palmon, R.P., Oct. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Shackelford, E.M., Oct. 7, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Bruce, Will C., Oct. 10, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Ledbetter, Oct. 17, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Hendrickson, John J., Oct. 27, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Hirst, C.M., Oct. 27, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Laird, P.E., Oct. 27, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Nichols, G.R., Oct. 27, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Smith, J.F., Oct. 27, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Willingham, H.J., Oct. 27, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Ivy, H.M., Oct. 28, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Oct. 31, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Ivy, H.M., Oct. 31, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Smith, J.F., Oct. 31, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rawlins, H.A., Nov. 8, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Maxey, F.S., Nov. 11, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Blakeley, H.B., Nov. 14, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Ivy, H.M., Nov. 14, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Willingham, Henry J., Nov. 14, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Frank H., Nov. 23, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Smith, J.H., Nov. 26, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Allen, C.H., Dec. 8, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Blakeley, H.B., Dec. 8, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Farrington Co., Dec. 8, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Smith, J.F., Dec. 8, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Nichols, Mrs. G.R., Dec. 13, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Willingham, Henry J., Dec. 14, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Board of Education, Dec. 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Ivy, H.M., Dec. 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Simmons, George C., Dec. 16, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Reiff, E.K., Dec. 30, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Dec. 30, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Adair, Cornelia S., Jan. 3, 1928 (Box 3)
  - O'Harrow, Omar, Jan. 23, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Stigler, Oren, Jan. 23, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rochelle, W.L., Feb. 3, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rochelle, W. L., Feb. 8, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Abbott, T.C., Feb. 13, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Heidelberg, H.B., Feb. 13, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Feb. 28, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Challman, Samuel H., March 28, 192 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., March 28, 192 (Box 3)
  - Hirst, C.M., April 2, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rochelle, W.R., April 9, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Cherry, T.C., April 18, 1928 (Box 3)
  - University of North Carolina, April 23, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, April 27, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., April 28, 1928 (Box 4)
  - O'Shea, M.V., May 3, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., May 12, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Bachman, Frank P., May 15, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, May 18, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Frank H., May 18, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., May 29, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, June 2, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, June 11, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, June 25, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., June 28, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Challman, Samuel A., July 7, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Cherry, T.C., July 18, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Echols, W.G., July 20, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Edwards, John H., July 23, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Whaley, Nell, July 27, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, July 28, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., July 28, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Upton, R.G., Aug. 2, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, Aug., 9, 1928 (Box 3)
  - National Motion Pictures Co., Aug. 17, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Orchard, Lucille, Aug. 17, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Thomas, D.E., Aug. 17, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Upton, R.G., 17/08/28 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Frank H., Aug. 17, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Overton, John, Aug. 23, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Bruce, William C., Aug. 24, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, Aug. 24, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Frank H., Aug. 27, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, Aug. 29, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Aug. 29, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Sept. 7, 1928 (Box 3)
  - O'Steen, Myrtle, Sept. 7, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Shaw, O.A., Sept. 7, 1928 (Box 3)
  - McCracken, C.C., Sept. 17, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Tidwell, R.E., Sept. 17, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Whaley, Nell, Sept. 17, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Thomas, D.E., Sept. 18, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Tidwell, R.E., Sept. 18, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, Sept. 25, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Sept. 28, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Horn, J.F., Oct. 5, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Whaley, Nell, Oct. 15, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., Oct. 29, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Oct. 29, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Whaley, Nell, Nov. 2, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, Nov. 20, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Nov. 28, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Heidelberg, H.B., Dec. 12, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Walker, Dora D., Dec. 24, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., Dec. 29, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Miller, J.C., Dec. 31, 1928 (Box 3)
  - Saunders, G.W., Jan. 5, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, Jan. 8, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Thomas, D.E., Jan. 8, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Camp, Annie, Jan. 10, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Tingle, Ruby, Jan. 10, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Nessley, Carl T., Jan. 12, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Horn, J. Fred, Jan. 15, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Border, Clara V., Jan. 16, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Byrne, Thomas W., Jan. 16, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Walker, Dora Dee, Jan. 16, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Haddon, S.T., Jan. 30, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., Jan. 30, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Eckles, W.G., Feb. 1, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Feb. 1, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Challman, Samuel A., Feb. 7, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Hasekll, Feb. 7, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Tidwell, R.E., Feb. 15, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Feb. 16, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 22, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Frazier, John M., Feb. 22, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Harvard Univ. Fellowship Cmte., Feb. 26, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Feb. 28, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Bass, E.E., March 27, 192 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., March 29, 192 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Frank H., April 5, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Donovan, John J., April 6, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Howell, William H., AprilS, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., April 11, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Barton, Eva, April 12, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Challman, Samuel, April 15, 1929 (Box 3)
  - MA Dept. of Public Health, April 19, 1929 (Box 3)
  - KS State Dept. of Education, April 19, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Bruce, William C., April 25, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Moehlman, A.B., April 26, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Sellers, Minnie, April 26, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., April 29, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., April 29, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Bruce, William C., April 30, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Graham, James L., May 1, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Graham, James L., May 1, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Endsley, J.R., May 2, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Smith, S.L., May 4, 1929 (Box 3)
  - U.S. Supervising Architect, May 7, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Graham, James L., May 8, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Buice, W.A., May 10, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Triest, R.M., May 10, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Farmer, Dr., May 13, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Graham, James L., May 13, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Graham, James L., May 15, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Donovan, John J., May 20, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., May 29, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Peterson, Kimbark, June 7, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Phelps, Shelton, June 7, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Lay, Isabel R., June 14, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Stankard, Katherine E., June 14, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Crabb, A.L., June 28, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., June 28, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., June 28, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Shumate, Mamie, June 28, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., June 29, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rose, Thelma, July 5, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Schuyler, Paul M., July 9, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Moehlman, A.B., July 10, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Roemer, Joseph, July 11, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Moehlman, A.B., July 15, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Moehlman, Dr. and Mrs. A.B., July 26, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Payne, Bruce R., July 27, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., July 31, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Schmidt, H.W., JUly 31, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Hollis, L.P., Aug. 9, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Hirst, C.M., Aug. 20, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Graham, W.F., Sept. 16, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Krill, J.J., Sept. 16, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Geiger, W.T.P., Sept. 17, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Branch, Fannie, Sept. 19, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Caswell, Ellie, Sept. 20, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Gregory, Mrs. Irwin 0., Sept. 20, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Challman, Samuel H., Sept. 23, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Green, Eloise, Sept. 23, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Hutchinson, Iva, Sept. 23, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Sept. 23, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., Sept. 28, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Goodykoontz, Bess, Oct. 10, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Oct. 10, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Betel, James 0., Oct. 28, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Carpenter, W.W., Oct. 28, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Krill, J.J., Oct. 28, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., Oct. 30, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 2, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 6, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Towner, Isabel L., Nov. 11, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Evans, Henry R., Nov. 13, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 15, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 19, 1929 (Box 3)
  - McCornack, W.R., Nov. 19, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Schmidt, H.W., Nov. 19, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Blair, John J., Nov. 21, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Pruett, Haskell, Nov. 21, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 22, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Russon, L.P., Nov. 22, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Evans, Henry R., Nov. 24, 1929 (Box 3)
  - McCornack, Walter R., Nov. 24, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Wynn, William T., Nov. 26, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., Nov. 29, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Bristol, L.R., Nov. 30, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rice, Elwood E., Dec. 1, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Upson, Arthur T., Dec. 1, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Doster, James J., Dec. 2, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Scherer, Francis R., Dec. 2, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Dennis, John C., Dec. 3, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Finegan, Thomas E., Dec. 4, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.H., Dec. 6, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Dec. 9, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Prall, C.E., Dec. 10, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Bristol, L.R., Dec. 11, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Prall, C.A., Dec. 27, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Evans, Henry R., Dec. 30, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Dec. 30, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Coope, W.J., Dec. 31, 1929 (Box 3)
  - Bachman, Dr., undated (Box 3)
  - Betelle, James 0., undated (Box 3)
  - Boykin, J.C., undated (Box 3)
  - Braden, W.H., undated (Box 3)
  - Burroughs, Nannie H., undated (Box 3)
  - Burton, A. C., undated (Box 3)
  - Clark, Walter E., undated (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., undated (Box 3)
  - Commissioner of Education, undated (Box 3)
  - Considine, Miss, undted (Box 3)
  - Coolidge, C.E., undated (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Frank Irving, undated (Box 3)
  - Cubberly, Ellwood P., undated (Box 3)
  - Delima, A., undated (Box 3)
  - Eitel, H.C., undated (Box 3)
  - Holland, E.O., undated (Box 3)
  - Jones, E.W., undated (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., undated (Box 3)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., undated (Box 3)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, undated (Box 3)
  - McClure, John M., undated (Box 3)
  - Maphis, Charles G., undated (Box 3)
  - Mulligan, Mr., undated (Box 3)
  - Payne, Dr., undated (Box 3)
  - Peterson, E.A., undated (Box 3)
  - Pratt, Mr., undated (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., undated (Box 3)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, undated (Box 3)
  - Sibley, Mr., undated (Box 3)
  - State of ALabama, undated (Box 3)
  - Tigert, J.J., undated (Box 3)
  - Urquhart, James B., undated (Box 3)
  - Watkins and Watkins, undated (Box 3)
  - Wilbur, G. Elmer, undated (Box 3)
  - Wood, Thomas D., undated (Box 3)
  - Wright, Mr., undated (Box 3)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 3)